vitamindcouncil.org 2013-03-24

# Vitamin D Council > Privacy Policy

## Privacy policy

The Vitamin D Council is committed to protecting the privacy of our newsletter subscribers as well as all of our online guests. We adhere to the following policies:

### E-mail addresses

E-mail addresses collected for our monthly newsletter will be used solely for the purpose of monthly deliveries of our newsletter. The Vitamin D Council will never sell or share with any third party the email addresses of our subscribers, except where required by law. At any time our subscribers are free to cancel their subscription to our newsletter, upon which time the Vitamin D Council will cease all deliveries to said email address.

E-mail addresses submitted through a direct email to one, or both, of:  
info@vitamindcouncil.org  
webmaster@vitamindcouncil.org  
will be used solely as a means of providing a response to said communication, and will not be shared with any third party nor will they be used for any other purpose.

### Cookies

The web site monitors access to the site for the purpose of system administration of the web server and statistical monitoring of web site usage. This may include 'cookies'. A cookie is a message given to a web browser by a web server. The message is then stored by the browser in a text file called cookie.txt. Every time the browser obtains a page from the server this cookie message is sent back. A cookie can be used to identify users and personalize their visit by customizing web pages for them.

### Financial information

Any financial information such as credit card numbers, bank account information, or other data obtained for donation purposes will be used solely to process the transaction agreed upon and for no other purposes. Vitamin D Council does not sell or share this information with any third parties. This data may be viewed by us as well as by Click and Pledge, the service used by Vitamin D Council to facilitate these transactions.

### Methods we use to protect your information

We use security software to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. In addition, our business practices are reviewed periodically for compliance with policies and procedures governing the security and confidentiality of our information. Our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons.

### Children

This website does not provide services or sell products to children under the age of 18. [If you are under 18, you may use this website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.]

### How you can access your information

You can request access to all your personally identifiable information by sending an e-mail to info@vitamindcouncil.org.

### Consent

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

If our Privacy Policy or procedures change, we will immediately post those changes to our website. Any such changes will be effective immediately upon being posted, unless otherwise stated in the change.

### Effective date

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 18th May 2011.   

### Contacting The Vitamin D Council

Should you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of The Vitamin D Council or its online service, or any other aspects of this website, you are welcome to contact us at the address or email addresses below.

The Vitamin D Council does not respond to requests for medical advice (see disclaimer).

The Vitamin D Council  
1241 Johnson Ave. #134  
San Luis Obispo, California, United States  
93401  
info@vitamindcouncil.org  
webmaster@vitamindcouncil.org   

This privacy policy covers the Vitamin D Council web site at www.vitamindcouncil.org. Any links from these sites to other web sites are not covered by this policy.

Page last edited: 16 May 2011
